Sync:YTET-Vicky8800 & starry     -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
甚至在卡特里娜飓风席卷新奥尔良后的 几个月里
Even all these months after katrina ravaged the city of new orleans,
human remains are being found in devastated neighborhoods around the city.
市郊的废墟中仍然不断地发现遇难者的尸体
Cadaver dogs are being used to search for 2,300 people still unaccounted for.
搜索犬被用来寻找至今仍然失踪的2300人
Makeshift morgues still exist in warehouses,schools and churches throughout the area.
临时设置的太平间仍然遍布这一地区 的仓库, 学校和教堂中
Officials are finally beginning to admit what many people have know since the levees broke long ago:
官方终于承认了那些自从大堤垮塌以来 许多人就已经知道的事
Many of these people will never be found.
许多人永远也找不到了
You look tired,mike.Late night?
你看起来很累, Mike, 昨晚熬夜了?
Oh,yeah.Late and nasty.
噢, 是的，不仅晚而且脏啊
Same kinky creature?
还是一样的古怪的人?
Doc,the girl carries a serious perv swerve.
医生, 这个女孩很性感哦
Feeling wrong feels so good.
知道错了的感觉真好
Hey,sorry,dr. Brennan.
嘿, 抱歉, Brennan 博士
No,it's fine.Males often bond by exaggerating sexual conquests.
没事, 男人总喜欢夸大在性征服方面的事
Oh,mike's not exaggerating.
噢, Mike可没有夸张
This girl is seriously turned on by coffins.
这女孩的欲火被棺材严重的点燃了
Mike'll take her into the cooler in...
Mike带她到冰柜...
doc. --Some libidos are enflamed by a proximity to death.
- 医生 - 有人在濒临死亡的时候欲火会被点燃
Who's that?
那是谁？
My assistant,zack.Back in dc.
我的助手, Zack, 在华盛顿的后援
Congratulations on your coffin sex.
恭喜你奸尸
I've got work to do.
我还有事要做
Some of the information you've sent for analysis
你送来分析的一些信息
seems to have come from remains that have already been embalmed.
好像是来自那些已经防腐处理的尸体
The bodies were unearthed by the flooding.
这些尸体在洪水来的时候还没安葬
They have to be id'd and reburied.
他们需要进行身份鉴定后再重新埋葬
Could fly down there to help,dr. Brennan.
我可以飞来帮忙, Brennan博士
A: Tomorrow's my last day,and b:
第一: 明天是我的最后一天, 其次
The sex on the coffin thing is not guaranteed.
奸尸的事可不能保证哦
You know,there are reasons they call this the big easy--
你知道, 他们说这个极容易是有原因的
even after hurricane katrina.
甚至在卡特里娜飓风以后
Dr. Brennan.
Brennan博士
Meet john doe 361.
来见见无名氏361号
We found this one in the ninth ward,sticking out of the mud.
我们在第九区找到这个, 从泥土中伸出来
Good afternoon,detective harding.
下午好, Harding侦探
Male,40s.
男性, 40多岁
Badly decomposed.Looks pretty banged up.
严重腐烂, 看起来摔得很严重
Yep. Be nice to know if it was hurricane,flood or foul play that killed him.
是啊, 真想知道他是被飓风, 洪水 还是人杀的
Detective harding,have you been into the cooler lately?
Harding侦探, 最近你去过冷库吗？
Apparently,some libidos are enflamed by the proximity to death.
显然的, 濒临死亡时欲火会被点燃
God,graham.
上帝啊, Graham
Thinking about sex in this place should be illegal,if it ain't already.
在这个地方想着性应该是违法的 如果还不是的话
Oh,sam,I'm going to need x-rays on this one.
噢, Sam, 我需要对这个进行X光检查
Uh,looks like there's something lodged behind his teeth.
呃, 看起来在他牙齿后面存留了一些东西
You been working 48 hours straight.
你已经连续工作了48个小时了
You need an evening off.
你需要休息一晚上
I only have one vacation day left.
我只剩下一天假期了
What are you,doing penance for fema?
你是什么, 为联邦应急管理局苦修?
Why don't you let me cook you dinner tonight?
你为什么不让我今晚为你做晚餐呢?
I don't know.
我不知道
Come on.I'm a southern gentleman,ma'am.
得了, 我是一名南方的绅士, 女士
Your honor will be respected.
你应该受到尊敬
Tell you what,graham.
告诉你吧, Graham
We'll see what the x-rays tell us about this one and then,maybe...
我们来看看X光显示的关于这具尸体的 然后, 也许...
we'll get a bite to eat.
我们会去吃点东西
dr. Brennan,your airport shuttle is here.
Brennan博士, 你的机场接送车来了
What?
什么?
No,um...
不, 呃...
my flight isn't until thursday.
我的飞机是在星期四
Today is thursday,dr. Brennan.
今天就是星期四, Brennan博士
what happened to wednesday?
星期三发生了什么?
Dr. Brennan? Hello?Are you there,dr. Brennan?
Brennan博士? 喂? 你还在吗, Brennan博士?
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: chambers&macready&barry&superclark&布瓜&vicky怪 校对: sybil 时间轴:vicky8800 & starry
识骨寻踪 第一季 第十九集
Looks like someone stole your earring.
看起来有人偷了你的耳环
Ripped it right out of the lobe.
直接从耳垂上拉下来的
I don't know what happened to me.
我不知道我发生了什么事
It's a tough town.
这是一个难搞的地方
We don't have that many cops anymore,and,uh,
我们不再有那么多的警察, 而且, 呃
they were never that good to begin with.
他们也不值得加人手
Shouldn't insult the ones that stuck around.
不应该侮辱就在旁边的人
Detective harding,I didn'T...
Harding侦探, 我不...
know who else to call.
知道还能给谁打电话
I need blood samples on this clothing.
我需要这件衣服上的血液样本
Maybe we'll get lucky and they won't all come from you.
也许我们能走运这些血不全是你的
Still hazy on the details?
还对详情朦胧不清吗?
Not "hazy" on the details,I...
并不是对详情朦胧不清, 我...
I don't remember anything.
我什么也想不起来了
Nothing?
什么事都想不起来了吗?
Dr. Legiere knocking over a tray of instruments at the morgue.Then...
Legiere博士在太平间打翻了器械盘, 然后...
nothing.
什么都想不起了
That was the day before yesterday.
那是前天的事了
I requested a rape kit.
我要了一个强奸检查工具包
No sign of sexual activity,forced or otherwise.
没有性行为的痕迹, 被迫的或是其它的
Bones,you okay?
Bones, 你还好吗?
Booth,I told you not to come.
Booth, 我告诉过你不要来
Who's this?
这是谁？
He's fbi.We're sort of partners.
他是FBI, 我们算是拍档吧
Guy flies down from dc?You're more than sort of.
从华盛顿飞来的家伙, 交情不仅是算是吧
Yeah,that's great.You remember anything?
是的, 那很好, 你还记得什么吗?
A tray falling over.
一个器械盘掉了下来
Why can't she remember anything?
她为什么什么也记不得了?
Well,it could be the head injury.
嗯, 应该是头部受伤了
Hairline stress fracture on my right distal radius.
重压使我的右桡骨末梢骨折
Concussion,slight fever,torn earlobe.
脑震荡, 低烧, 耳垂撕裂
I lost one of my favorite earrings.
我丢失了我最喜欢的一只耳环
You're worried about an earring?
你为一只耳环担心?
You should really be worried about losing a whole day.
你应该是为丢失了整整一天而忧虑
I know,it's stupid,but these earrings were my mother'S.
我知道这很愚蠢可笑 但这些耳环是我妈妈留给我的
Amnesia caused by any traumatic event,injury or drug
由外伤, 药物引致的失忆
can erase memories before the event,not just after.
能够抹去事发之前的记忆, 并不仅仅是事后
Great,we'll just wait for a tox screen.
好的, 我们正在等待一个毒物报告
It's gonna be at least 24 hours.--24 hours?
- 这个要至少24小时 - 24小时?
Well,most of the labs in the area were destroyed by the hurricane.
好了, 这一地区的多数实验室 都在飓风中被毁了
We'll find out what happened.
我们会找出到底是怎么回事
You justake care of your,uh,partner.
你只需要照顾好你的, 呃, 拍档
Another present from the bayou.
从河口来的又一份礼物
I keep asking for a baby till that says "the big easy."
在听说"很容易"以前 我一直在寻找一个婴儿
Oh,we're all hoping for that.
噢, 我们都在盼望那个
For you,I mean.
为了你, 我是说
Does our funding allow us to do dr. Brennan's vacation work?
我们的经费允许 我们做Brennan的假期工作吗?
Uh,we're just doing what the feds didn'T.
呃, 我们只是在做这些FBI不做的
It's the yin-yang of government spending.
这就是政府开销的"阴阳性"
So we're sneaking?
这样说来我们是隐匿的?
That's what makes it fun.
这就是有趣的地方
John doe 361.
无名氏361号
Well,bad things happened to mr. Doe.
好, Doe先生遭遇了一些不好的事
It'll come back,bones.
它还会回来的, Bones
You don't know that.Head injuries are extremely unpredictable.
你不知道, 头部伤害是及其不可预知的
I'm just being reassuring.
我是为了更可靠
Brennan.
Brennan
Regarding the x-rays of john doe 361.
关于无名氏361号的X光片
John doe 361?
无名氏361号?
Yes,you sent his x-rays.
是的, 你发来的X光片
I don't remember that.
我不记得那个了
You don't remember?
你不记得了?
What about the x-rays,zack?
X光片怎样, Zack?
Male,late 40s,mixed race.
男性, 接近50岁, 混血儿
Anomalies on his spine,which I'm looking into,but the point is,
脊柱有异常, 我正在研究, 但关键是
his death was not accidental.
他并非意外死亡
I sent you the x-rays of a murder victim?
我给你发来了一个谋杀受害人的X光片?
How'd he die?
他怎么死的?
Is that booth?
是Booth吗?
Yes.
是的
You're hopping the streetcar named desire with booth?
你和Booth在那辆名叫欲望的街车里混吗?
Oh,I love this.
噢, 我喜欢这样
Obviously,they're working the murder of john doe 361 together.
明显地, 他们正在一起寻找 杀死无名氏361号的凶手
Precisely.How did 361 die?
非常正确, 361号是怎么死的?
The pelvis shows crush fractures.
骨盆显示被压碎
There's also what appears to be a bullet hole in the skull,but there's no exit wound.
还显示头骨上有一个弹孔 但是没有子弹射出造成的伤口
Okay,keep working on it.
好, 继续干
You don't remember the case?
你不记得这件事了吗?
No. And it's a murder.
不记得, 而且这是一件谋杀
God,I'm hungry.
噢, 我饿了
Well,when was the last time you ate?
你最后一次吃东西是什么时候?
Oh,my bad.You have amnesia.
噢, 我忘了, 你失忆了
Booth,I think I know a place.
Booth, 我想我知道一个地方
All right,so what is the last thing that you do remember?
好吧, 那么你最后一件记得的事是什么？
I told you,graham:Dr. Legiere knocked over a tray of surgical instruments.
我告诉过你了, Graham 也就是Legiere博士打翻了外科器械盘
I want to talk to legiere.
我想和Legiere谈谈
We must have been about to examine john doe 361.
我们必须去检查无名氏361号
Dr. Brennan.
Brennan博士
I thought you were leaving today?
我以为你今天要走?
Peter,this is my friend seeley booth.
Peter, 这是我的朋友Seeley Booth
My god,what happened to you?
天哪, 你怎么了?
I'm not certain,but the...the bruising suggests tuesday night.
我也不知道, 但...这瘀伤 显示是星期二的晚上
After you left here?
在你离开这儿以后?
I was here tuesday?--What time?
- 我星期二在这儿? - 什么时间?
In at 8:00,left at 9:00.
8点来, 9点走的
Don't you remember?You had dinner with sam potter.
你不记得了吗?  你和Sam Potter一起吃的晚餐
Bones.
Bones
We have to go back to the morgue,talk to sam.
我们必须回太平间, 和Sam谈谈
Who's sam? --He's an orderly.He practices voodoo.
- 谁是Sam? - 他是个勤务兵，他信奉伏都教
Hey,wait up,bones.
嘿, 等一下, Bones
You invited me to dinner.
你邀请我吃晚餐
Why?
为什么?
You found this in the mouth of a john doe.
你在无名氏的口中发现了这个
Let me see that.
让我看看
That's voodoo?
那是伏都诅咒?
It's gris-gris bag.It's a mojo.
那是个护身符, 也是个符咒
This one is meant to silence the dead so they can't speak.
这个是用来使死者沉默, 什么也不能说
Well,usually dead people are pretty much silent on their own.
但是, 通常死人主动的都非常沉默了
Voodoo embraces the premise that
伏都信奉这样一个假定
spirits can speak to us from beyond the grave.
灵魂能在阴间对我们讲话
Voodoo is all about the balance of the forces.
伏都全是关于力量的平衡
That wind,the flood,this death,it's all out of balance now.
风, 洪水, 死亡, 这些现在都失去平衡了
Katrina was armageddon for the ones who love balance.
卡特里娜是爱好平衡的人的Armageddon  (圣经中世界末日善恶决战的战场)
Some think it was secte rouge that brought it on.
有些人认为是红宗带来的
What's that,some kind of a gang?
那是什么, 某种分支吗?
The ones who follow evil.
那些追随邪恶的人
Some believe that they purposely angered the sirens who sent the flood.
有人认为是他们故意激怒了Sirens  (希腊神话中的女海妖), 带来了洪水
This,this is secte rouge.
这, 这就是红宗
Okay,so that's literally bad voodoo.
好的, 那么就是完全坏的伏都
It's black gum root.
这是黑胶鸡脚
There's only one place you can find it:
只在一个地方你可以找到它:
A voodoo shop on pontchartrain avenue,run by richard benoit.
在Pontchartrain大道的一个伏都商店 由Richard Benoit运营
He's a good man.Maybe he can help you.
他是个好人, 也许他可以帮助你
Okay,thanks.
好的, 谢谢了
Dr. Brennan,a lost day?
Brennan博士, 丢失了一天?
Perhaps a spell was cast on you as well.
也许一个符咒已经给你披上了
No disrespect,sam,but it's not my religion.
不是不尊敬, Sam, 但这不是我的信仰
Come on,booth.
来吧, Booth
Voodoo-- who's gonna believe that stuff?
伏都--谁会相信那种东西?
It's a religion,no crazier than...
那是一种信仰, 并不比...更疯狂
well,what are you?
好, 你信什么?
Catholic.
天主教
They believe in the same saints you do,in prayer...
他们和你信仰同样的圣人, 祈祷...
what they call spells,you call miracles.They have priests.
他们管那个叫符咒, 你叫奇迹 他们有牧师
Yeah,we don't make zombies.
是的, 但我们不进行还魂术
Jesus rose from the dead after three days.
耶稣死后三天又复活
brennan.--Jesus is not a zombie.
- Brennan - 耶稣不是蛇神(伏都教崇拜的神灵)
All right? Man.I shouldn't have to tell you that.
好吗? 我干吗要告诉你这些
On john doe 361,there's a narrowing of the disc space on l2 and l3.
关于无名氏361号, 在椎间盘 第12和13椎骨间有一个断面收缩
Congenital?
天生的?
Unclear.
不清楚
Extensive injuries consistent with a body being thrown around by a flood.
大面积的受伤符合一个尸体 在洪水中被冲击的事实
Cross-reference what you know so far with the d-mort records of missing katrina victims.
前后对照目前为止你所知道的 卡特里娜飓风里的受害者
Hey,brennan.
嘿, Brennan
Why haven't you come home?
你怎么还不回家？
Pretty soon,ange.
就快了, Ange
Is booth there socially?
Booth在那儿善于交际吗?
Of course not.
当然不是
All right,what's going on?
好吧, 那是怎么了?
Hey,bones has amnesia because a voodoo murderer put a spell on her
嘿, Bones失忆了 因为有个伏都杀手给她下了符咒
to keep her from solving the murder of john doe 361.
让她不能参与解决 谋杀无名氏361号的凶手
That's a huge supposition.
那是一个巨大的推测
That's fine if you don't want to tell me.
如果你不愿意告诉我就算了
ha. Voodoo amnesia.
哈, 伏都健忘
It's a good one.
是个好东西
Yeah. It's great.Brennan's fighting zombies in new orleans.
耶, 真棒 Brennan正在新奥尔良与蛇神战斗
And we're stuck here.
而且我们呆在这儿
Oh,what's that smell?
噢, 什么味道？
I imagine everything smells in here.
我想这的所有东西都有味道
please just tell me that that car survived katrina.
请告诉我那辆车在卡特丽娜中幸存了
we used it to evacuate.
我们用它来疏散
Did you restore it yourself,or did you use,uh,voodoo?
你是自己修复的, 还是用, 呃, 伏都?
an unbeliever.
一个不相信者
What can I do for you?
我能为你们做什么?
You,uh...you know what that is?
你, 呃...你知道那是什么吗?
This is a dark spell.Forbidden magic,very strong.
是一个黑暗符咒，禁忌魔法, 非常强
This is secte rouge.
这是红宗的
I certainly wouldn't make anything like this.
我肯定不会做这样的东西
But you have the ingredients here.
但你这儿有原料
Well,the individual ingredients are not malignant.
单独的成分并不是恶性的
It is how they are combined
关键他们怎样被组合的
and what intention they are used for that makes a spell good or bad.
还有他们被使用的目的 是做一个好的符咒还是坏的
Do you recognize me?
你认识我吗?
No. Should I?
不，我应该吗?
Anyone else work here?
这还有谁做事?
My daughter,eva.
我女儿, Eva
What is this about?
这是干嘛?
We're conducting an investigation.
我们在做一个调查
Eva!What kind of investigation?
Eva! 什么样的调查?
Is it true that this is the only place a person can buy black gum root?
这是唯一一个可以买到黑胶鸡脚的地方 是真的吗?
Yes. Most places like this are all gone now.
是， 大多数像这样的地方现在都没了
It's not a coincidence.
这不是巧合
Yes,daddy?
爸爸?
Have you ever seen this lady before?
你以前看过这位女士吗?
No. Why?
没有，为什么?
We need to know who's bought this lately?
我们需要知道最近谁买过这个?
Don't they need a warrant?
他们不需要搜查证么?
Eva will pull up what you need on the computer.
Eva会在电脑上找出你们想要的东西
Eva...
what you said before.What'd you mean it's just a coincidence?
你刚才说什么来着 它只是个巧合是什么意思?
Most places like this where a houngan,a priest,can get what he needs--
大多数象这样可以让一个祭师, 一个牧师 得到他所需要的东西的地方--
they are all gone now.
现在全都没了
Because of the hurricane and flood.
因为飓风和洪水的关系
Which occurred because of a lack of balance.
这些都是缺乏平衡而发生的灾难
Mr. Benoit,
Benoit先生
are you suggesting that secte rouge somehow conjured up a hurricane?
你是在暗示说不管怎样 红宗可以召唤来一场飓风?
Secte rouge voodoo is much more powerful than ours.
伏都红宗比我们的教派强大多了
No,eva.Not more powerful.
不，Eva，不是更强大
Destruction is easier than harmony,but not more powerful.
破坏比调和简单多了 但并不见得更强大
There are a lot of misunderstandings about voodoo.
关于伏都教有太多的误解了
Yeah,I know that whole zombie stuff puts a crimp in your public relations,I bet.
是啊, 我知道那整个蛇神的事情给 你们与公众的关系造成了阻碍
These are the people who bought black gum root in the past month.
这些是上个月买过黑胶鸡脚的人
Graham legiere,the medical examiner.
Graham Legiere, 那个验尸的
I tried to get in touch with him.
我试着跟他联系
He was scheduled to be out in the field this week.
他计划本周会外出去实地工作
Graham?It's temperance.
Graham? 是Temperance
What if he's not here?
他要是不在这儿呢?
He's probably asleep.He's been working nights.
他可能在睡觉, 他熬了几个通宵
Graham!
Graham?
Cracker.
闯入者
Hey,that's not funny.
嘿, 那一点都不好笑
I think he invited me to dinner that night,or drinks.Can't remember.
我想那天晚上他请我去吃晚饭 或者喝什么东西, 记不清了
You know what?Maybe he roofied you.
你知道吗? 也许他给你下了迷药
I'm sure he bought the black gum root to look into its medicinal qualities.
我肯定他买黑胶鸡脚 是为了研究它的医理作用
Yeah,because we all know how effective that is.
是啊, 我们都知道那多有效
Voodoo healing is quite effective.
伏都治疗是相当有效的
No crazier than acupuncture or exorcism.
并不比针灸或驱魔咒更疯狂
Hey,hey. Easy on the catholics.Okay? Just easy.
嘿, 嘿, 别老盯着天主教好吗?  放松点
Bones.
Bones
There you go again.
你又来了
Bones!
Are you okay?
你还好吗?
Something bad happened here.
这儿发生过什么不好的事情
They got away.
他们逃脱了
Something bad.
是不太好
What exactly were you doing here?
你刚才到底在这儿干吗?
It's graham,isn't it?
那是Graham, 对不对?
Tell you what,dr. Brennan.I'm going to ask the questions.
Brennan博士, 我要问问题了
Oh,come on,detective.She was working with the guy.
哦, 嘿, 侦探, 她和那个男的是同事
How closely?
关系有多亲近?
What's that supposed to mean?
那是什么意思?
Answer my question,please.
请回答我的问题
What brought you here?
你为什么来这儿?
Was it a social call? Business?Revenge killing?
是正常社交? 公事? 仇杀?
Look,legiere bought some black gum root from the voodoo store.We just stopped by to ask why.
Legiere在伏都商店买了一些黑胶鸡脚 我们只是来问问为什么
Why?
为什么?
That's what we came here to ask.
那就是我们来这儿要问的
You want to look behind me and remind yourselves
你们想看看我后面来提醒你们自己
why I'm a little low on sense of humor?
为什么我的幽默感有点迟钝么?
What? That wasn't a joke.
什么? 那不是个笑话
All right,she's not wisecracking.She just tends to be a bit,you know,literal.
好吧, 她不是在说俏皮话 她只是有点喜欢, 你知道, 咬文嚼字
Day before yesterday I showed a voodoo expert a mojo
前天我给一个伏都专家看了一个符咒
that graham found lodged in the mouth of john doe 361.
就是Graham 在无名氏361号的嘴里发现的
This,uh,voodoo consultation.Did it occur before or after amnesia?
这个, 呃, 伏都咨询 是在你失忆之前还是之后?
The amnesia's real.
她是真的失忆
Graham purchased a rare ingredient at a voodoo shop on pontchartrain ave.
Graham在Pontchartrain大街的一家 伏都商店购买了一种很罕见的成分
So graham made voodoo spells,shoved them into corpse's mouths
所以Graham下了伏都诅咒 把他们塞进尸体的嘴里
and pretend to be surprised when he found them?
然后再找到他们的时候 装成很惊讶的样子?
What's that? --Split cast,huh?More voodoo,just like the symbol on the wall.
- 那是什么?  - 断掉的铸件, 阿?  更多的伏都东西了, 就像墙上的符号一样
Bag it as evidence.
作为证据装起来
Secte rouge?
红宗?
What do you know about secte rouge?
关于红宗你知道什么?
If you're done with us,detective,we're going to go.
如果你问完了, 侦探, 我们要走了
I'm going to tear this place apart,
我会把这个地方掀个底朝天
and if I find one piece of evidence that ties you to the scene,
如果我找到一丁点可以让你 和犯罪现场有关联的证据
I will take you into custody.
我会拘捕你
Do you really think someone could go into a trance,
你真的认为会有人陷入这样失神的状态
commit a murder like that and not remember it?
犯下谋杀而什么都不记得?
No,I don'T.
不
But I sure as hell think someone can fake amnesia.
但我坚信有人可以装成失忆
That's great.Thank you,detective.
很好, 谢谢, 侦探
These files are everything you and graham worked on the day before yesterday.
这些文件就是你前天和Graham 在一起工作的全部东西
James,meet agent seely booth.
James, 见见Seely Booth探员
Dr. Embry is graham's second in command.
Embry博士是Graham的第一助手
Condolences on your sudden promotion.
关于你的突然升职我很悲痛
how do you think the job had anything to do with graham being killed?
你们怎么会觉得这个工作 会和Graham被杀有关?
Bones has voodoo amnesia;legiere is voodoo-dead;
Bones有伏都失忆症 Legiere是被伏都咒杀死的
and the last thing they worked on together was a voodoo ritual murder,
而他们最后一起工作的 是一个伏都仪式的谋杀者
so I'm thinking there might be some kind of a connection.
所以我以为这里面可能会有什么联系
Legiere's body--
Legiere的尸体--
is it,uh,bad as they say?
它是, 呃, 真的像他们说的那么糟?
How bad are they saying it is?
他们说有多糟?
No matter how bad they're saying it is,it's worse.
不管他们说的有多糟, 事实上是更糟
I just want to mentally prepare myself.
我只是想做好心理准备
I-I start his autopsy in a few minutes.
我-我要在几分钟后为他做尸检
The file I need is john doe 361.
我需要的文件是无名氏361号
According to the records,these are the only cases you worked on the day before yesterday.
根据记录, 你们前天一起做过的案子 就只有这些
Four sets of remains,two were easy ids,drown victims processed and booted for burial.
四具遗骸, 两具是简单的身份鉴定 按溺水受害者处理了, 装起来埋了
The other two were both males,john does 349 and 350.
另外两具是男性, 无名氏349号和350号
I sent 361's x-rays to the Jeffersonian.
我给Jeffersonian发过361号的X光片
Well,I'll check again.
我会再查一下
Can I make a lifestyle suggestion here? --Go ahead.
- 我能在这作一个生活方式的建议吗?  - 说吧
You know,"vacation"--it's from the latin,vacatio.
你知道吗, "度假(vacation)"  它来自拉丁语, vacatio
It means "freedom" or "release."You might want to consider that next time.
意思是 "自由" 或者 "释放" 也许你下次该想想这个
Learning latin?
学拉丁语?
This is the opposite of vacation.
这就像是度假的反义词
I mean,the one that you snapped,went insane and totally lost your mind.
我的意思是, 这个你突然中断 变得神经兮兮而且让你脑子完全失灵的假期
Oh,thanks for your understanding.
哦, 谢谢你的理解
Uh,dr. Brennan.There's no john doe 361.
呃, Brennan 博士, 没有无名氏361号
Then whose x-rays did I send to dc?
那么那些我发给博士的X光片是谁的呢?
No,I mean the file is gone.
没有, 我是说那些档案都没了
Oh... okay. I'll hold that.
哦...好, 保持通话
Zack addy.
Zack Addy
Zack,it's me. Anything else on john doe 361?
Zack, 是我, 关于无名氏361号有什么?
Yes,dr. Brennan,we found some damage to the pubic bone,some kind of strike marks.
是的, Brennan 博士 我们在耻骨发现一些损伤, 像是击打的痕迹
Did you get angela to reconstruct the pattern?
你让Angela去做模式重建了吗?
Yeah. Hi,sweetie. I'm here.
是的, 嗨, 甜心, 我在这儿
I tried to make a digital positive,but it didn't work.
我试过去做一个数字正片, 但是不起作用
Why? --It was voodoo,probably.
- 为什么?  - 也许是伏都
The extrapolation protocols can't resolve the gradient fluxes in the bone shadings.
推算协议无法解决骨阴影的梯度流量
What's that? --That's mumbo jumbo.It's scientific voodoo.
- 那是什么?  - 那是神奇的东西, 科学的伏都
Can you do them manually?
你能手工做吗?
Off an x-ray?
不用X光?
Mm... not really.
唔...恐怕不行
Can you send the actual remains?
你能把现在的遗骸送过来吗?
They don't exist.
他们不存在了
That makes no sense.
没道理啊
It was probably voodoo.
可能是伏都
Voodoo?
伏都?
Okay,quit saying "voodoo."
好了, 别再说 "伏都" 了
Yeah,because,you know it's not a factor.
是的, 因为, 你知道它和这没关系
Okay,let me know what you find. Bye.
行, 找到什么就告诉我们, 拜
How do we know this is not the guy shoving mojo bags into dead people?
我们怎么知道这不是把符咒塞给死者的人?
Those spells are the work of a sorcerer.
那些是一个男巫士的符咒
Priests-- houngans--can make healing motions mojoes,but I'm not allowed.
牧师--祭师--可以做治疗, 但是我不能
But snake shaking-- that's fine?
但是摇蛇--那就可以?
The snake pulls the evil out of the soul,freeing the spirit...
蛇把灵魂里的恶魔拖出来, 解放灵魂...
I must do what small things I can.
我必须做力所能及的
The floods washed away too much of what was good.
洪水冲走了太多好的东西
Hey,bones,how's about while you're a murder suspect,
嗨, Bones, 你现在可是杀人嫌疑犯
you,uh,act more like a normal woman and less like lily munster,okay?
你, 呃, 表现得像一个正常女人多一些 而不是魔女莉莉, 好吗?
Bye. Good snake.Bye-bye.
拜, 乖蛇, 再见
You know,call me crazy,but I'm suspicious of snake man.
你可以, 说我疯了 但是我怀疑那个耍蛇人
Oh! That's because you've been inculcated by
哦! 那是因为你被
the mainstream culture's prevailing judeo-christian tradition
主流文化中流行的犹太与基督教所共有的 传统教导长大的
into instinctive skepticism of alternative mores.
变得本能地会对二者之外的 其他产生怀疑
Yeah. Thanks for that explanation.
是啊, 谢谢你的解释
I've been over every inch of these x-rays.
我已经仔细看过这些X光片了
Me,too.
我也是
There's evidence of particles on the bones,
骨头里有很细小的痕迹
but there is no way for me to know what they are.
但是我根本不知道那是什么
Probably dirt.
也许是灰尘
Yes,thank you,zack,
是的, 谢谢, Zack
but dirt is a meaningless word.
但是灰尘是废话
You can't see air on an x-ray.
你在X光片看不到空气
What?
什么?
I never said you could.
我从没说过你可以
What? I'm not even talking about air.
什么?我都没说起空气
You can see a space where air might be,
你可以看到空气所在的空间
like a cavity,but not the air itself.
像是一个腔, 但是不是空气本身
What I'm saying is that,yes,
我正在说的是, 是的
there are flecks on the x-ray that might be dirt,
在X光片下的斑点可能是灰尘
but that doesn't tell us anything.
但是那说明不了什么
Is it sandy,hmm?
是沙子吗, 恩?
Silty,humusy?
淤泥, 腐殖质?
Is it clay? Is it more organic than mineral?
那是粘土吗? 是比矿物质 更有活性的物质吗?
Is it soil? Is it pulverized gravel?
是土壤吗? 是砂砾粉吗?
What minerals are in it? Are the minerals crystalline?
它的成分是什么?  那矿物是晶体状的吗?
See,these are all details a person cannot get off an x-ray
看吧, 这些是一个人不能找到的细节
no matter how long he stares at it.
不管他盯着X光片看多久
Sometimes a person should look for things that aren't there
有时候一个人应该去找找不在的东西
instead of things that are there.
而不是只停留在表面
You mean me?
你说我吗?
In dirt?
只看到灰尘?
No. Me.
不, 是我
On the x-ray. I've been looking for anomalies which exist
看X光片 我一直在找存在的不寻常东西
instead of anomalies which don't exist.
而不是不存在的异常物
Zack,
Zack
if you are ever going to successfully mimic being human,
如果你曾想过要成功地做人的话
you have to stop making everything about you,and feign interest in the other guy.
你就得停止让一切都围着你转 然后假装对他人的事感兴趣
Zack!
I've noticed that you try to look taller.
我注意到你想看起来高点
When?
什么时候?
Around dr. Brennan.
在Brennan博士身边转的时候
I do not.
我没有
And angela,because they are both taller than you.
还有Angela, 因为她们都比你高
You know what?
你知道吗?
I take it back.
我收回我的话
Don't take any interest in the other guy.
不要对别人的事感兴趣
Thank you for your help.
谢谢你的帮助
So,do you remember anything else that could help us out?
你还记起其他什么有帮助的事吗?
It could have been me.
那可能是我
You remember that?
你记起那了?
Look at it objectively.
客观地看
Graham legiere was killed between 11:00 P.M tuesday and 3:00 A.M. Wednesday.
Graham Legiere是在周二晚上11:00 到周三早上3:00间被杀的
Not only do I not have an alibi,I...
不只是因为我没有不在场证据, 我...
I can't even explain to myself
我不能为我自己辩解
where I was.
我去过哪
It could have been me.
那可能是我
no,it couldn'T.
不, 不会的
Yes... wha...? How do you know?
是的...什...? 你怎么知道?
I just know,okay? I'd bet my professional career on it.
我就是知道, 行吗?  我以我的职业担保
I already did.
我已经做过了
- What? - Nothing.
- 什么?  - 没什么
- What did you do? - Bones...
- 你做过什么了?  - Bones...
stop.
够了
This is the last time and place that you want to be rational,okay?
这是你能记得的最后来的地方, 是吗?
Let's just be wildly emotional and assume
大胆地假定
that you didn't psychotically murder a co-worker who invited you over for dinner.
你没有精神错乱地杀了 邀请你吃饭的那个同僚
- What's that?  - What?
- 那是什么?  - 什么?
That.
那个
Ew...
咦...
it's another voodoo dumpling?
另一个伏都教的饺子吗?
It's some kind of flesh.
这是一些肉之类的东西
And these are seashells.
这些是贝壳
Leather,I think.
羽毛
Is that a human tooth?
那是人牙吗?
Yes. A canine.
是的, 一颗犬牙
put down your weapon,agent booth.
放下你的武器, Booth调查员
Put down your weapon. There's no threat from us.
放下你的武器, 我们没有恶意
You're holding a gun on me.
你举着枪对着我呢
Yeah,well,you know,my finger here is not on the trigger.
是的, 我的手指没在扳机上
It's the best I can do under the circumstances.
在这种情况下这是我最可以做的了
Holster your weapons.
收起你的武器
I'm here to arrest dr. Brennan for the murder of graham legiere.
我来这里是以谋杀Graham Legiere的罪名 逮捕Brennan博士的
Oh,that's not going to happen.
那可不行
Yeah,I'm pretty sure it is.
我肯定是能行的
I told you,booth.
我告诉过你, Booth
Bones,please!
Bones, 拜托了!
Just once in your life will you be quiet?
你能在一生中保持安静一次吗?
That's good advice because everything you say can and will be held against you in a court of law.
那是个好建议因为你说的一切 都将成为呈堂证供
What is that?
那是什么?
It's,uh... I found it on my pillow.
这是, 呃...我在我枕头边找到的
Bones!
thank you,dr. Brennan.
谢谢, Brennan博士
What's the probable cause?
什么原因使你来的?
Traces of dr. Brennan's blood in legiere's home,legiere's blood on her clothing.
Brennan博士的血的痕迹在Legiere家里 Legiere的血在她衣服上
From the clinic.
诊所的衣服
Is that it?
就这样?
All I'm prepared to share with the federal government.
所有我准备 和联邦政府分享的就这么多了
Now,please,step away from my collar.
现在，请不要干涉我的逮捕行动
I'm afraid I can't let that happen.
恐怕你不能如愿了
Bones! Geez!
Bones! 上帝啊!
It's better if nobody else dies while we get to the bottom of this.
如果这样就没其他人会死很好啊
Uh! Well,you know what? I wasn't planning on dying.
你知道吗? 我没想过死
Ow! It's not you i worry about.
啊! 我没有担心你
Ow!
啊!
You're welcome to the room. It's paid for.
你可以在这房间, 已经付过钱了
were you sleeping with graham legiere?
你和Graham Legiere睡过了吗?
I don'T...
我没有...
I don't think so.
我可不这么想
You don't think so?
你可不这么想?
I don't remember sleeping with him,and at the clinic,
我不记得和他睡过, 在医院里
they said there was no sign of sexual activity.
医生说过没有发生性行为的迹象
I hope you kept your mouth shut.
我希望你闭上你的嘴
Okay,temperance brennan,carolyn julian.
好了, Temperance Brennan Carolyn Julian
She's your lawyer. She's from the us attorney's office.
她是你的律师 她来自美国律师事务所
She's the best there is.
她是最好的
You found a prosecutor to defend her?
你找了一个起诉者来为她辩护?
Interesting tactic.
有意思的想法
I've told detective harding everything I know
我已经告诉侦探我知道一切了
- so far.  - She's a fool?
- 到目前为止  - 她是个笨蛋吗?
You didn't tell me she's a fool.
你没告诉我她是个笨蛋
No,she's a brilliant forensic anthropologist.
不, 她是一个很聪明的人类学家
Well,I have three degrees.
我有三个学位
I've pioneered research in...
我是...的先驱
what's that?
那是什么?
A gris-gris bag.
一个符咒包
I found it in my hotel... room...
我在旅馆的房间...找到的...
I'm assuming the person who left it there is trying to frame me,
我猜那个留下这东西的人 想要陷害我
so the tooth is probably graham'S.
所以那牙齿可能是Graham的
Three degrees and still a fool.
有三个学位的还是个笨蛋
This interview is over,rose.
审问结束了, Rose
I need to speak with my client alone before she gives herself a lethal injection.
在我的客户受到致命注射前 我要和她单独谈谈
Of course.
当然可以
It's nice seeing you again,carolyn.
很高兴再见到你, Carolyn
Okay,bones,what the hell were you talking to her for?
好了, Bones, 你到底和她说了些什么?
I was just trying to help.
我只是想帮忙
You sew those lips together,girl,
你闭上你的嘴, 姑娘
because there is no such thing as helping the new orleans police.
因为想要一个新奥尔良警察帮你 是不可能的事
They just want to close the case as quickly and easily as they can,
他们只想尽早简单地了结案子
and you are making it christmastime for them.
你正好撞到了枪口上了
Okay,listen,there's no way that bones could have killed legiere.
好吧, 听着 Bones不可能会杀了Legiere
I mean,it's just not her. I mean,look at her.
那不像她的作风, 看看她
I am doing you a favor taking this case,booth.
我正在帮你接手这个案子呢, Booth
But as the lady cop says,I'm a prosecutor.
但就像那个女警察说的 我是一个起诉者
And as it stands now,
现在看来
I could try this case in my pjs and still get a conviction.
有可能虽然我作这个案子 但是还是被宣布有罪
Well,shouldn't you get to know your clients before you make snap judgments?
在你武断下结论前 你不应该先了解一下你的客户吗?
Bones...
fine. Stop me when i get something wrong.
好吧, 当我说错的时候阻止我吧
Trained in three types of martial arts,
受过三种武术训练
two assault charges,
两种攻击技巧
registered marksman with the nra,
国家档案登记处的注册射手
hunting licenses in four states...
四个国家的狩猎许可证...
- you hunt? - Only for food.
- 你狩猎吗?  - 只是为找吃的
Shot an unarmed man.
射杀一个手无寸铁的人
He was trying to set me on fire.
他想要放火烧我
All right,just...
好吧, 只要...
just arrange bail for us,carolyn,
只要安排保释就行了, Carolyn
so we can get out of here.
那样我们能离开这里
Sure,sure.
当然了, 当然了
Don't want to get this one mad at me.
才不想让这家伙对我生气呢
Bones,you just couldn't keep your mouth shut,could you?
Bones, 你不能不说话吗?
I can identify this guy.
我可以鉴别出这家伙
You know,angela isn't that much taller than me.
Angela并不比我高多少
Spina bifida.
Spina Bifida
He had a shunt from his brain stem down to his heart.
子弹从他的头一直穿到他的心脏
It was removed more than a decade ago.
距离现在已经有十年之久了
We both like brussels sprouts.
我们俩都喜欢Brussels Sprouts
You don't like brussels sprouts.
你不喜欢Brussels Sprouts
A man can change,zack.
人总会变的, Zack
What,a human tooth?
什么, 一颗人牙?
Yeah,it was some kind of... some flesh,
是的, 这是些...肉之类的
some fabric; it looked like some kind of shell.
一些织物, 这看起来像是贝壳
Yeah,sounds like
是的, 像是
to make you forget.
能让你健忘
Somebody doesn't want you to know what happened to john doe 361.
有人不想你知道发生在无名氏361号的事
Booth,I'm not under a spell.
Booth, 我没被施咒
Well,you forgot a whole day.
你忘了一整天的事
The spirits don't need you to believe in them,dr. Brennan;
这些力量不需要你去相信它们 Brennan博士
they believe in you.
它们相信你
See you back at work,huh?
工作时再见, 呃?
How'd I get away?
我怎样脱离干系的?
You know,graham got killed.
Graham被杀了
I got away. How did I do that?
我没事了, 我是怎么做到的?
You know,bones,all those things that carolyn mentioned,
你知道, Bones, 所有Carolyn说的事
you know,the martial arts,the shooting,the assaults...
武术, 射击, 攻击术...
it's just you're just the type of woman that fights.
你就是那种善于出击的女人
Maybe they didn't expect it.
也许他们不这么认为
Maybe they thought some kind of magic could hold you.
也许他们认为什么魔法可以控制你
I don't believe in magic.
我不相信魔法
Exactly.
对头
You're a surprising woman. Sometimes that's enough for getting away.
你是个令人惊讶的女人  有时候那足以让你脱离干系了
Why are you nice to me?
你为什么对我这么好?
Because. Because they think they get away with it.
因为, 因为他们认为他们能处理得掉
What?
什么?
They burn their victim. They blow him up.
他们能烧了受害者, 他们能炸掉他
They toss him in the ocean.
他们能把他扔进大海
They bury them in the desert.
他们能把他埋在沙漠里
They throw 'em to wood chippers.
他们能扔进木材粉碎机里
Sometimes,you know,years go by,they relax.
有时候, 很多年后, 他们就解脱了
Then they start living their lives like they didn't do anything wrong.
然后他们重新生活 就像什么都没做过一样
Like they didn't spend somebody else's life in order to get what they got.
就像他们没有牺牲别人的命 来换取他们要的一样
They think they're safe from retribution,but you know...
他们认为他们不会得到报应了, 但是...
you make those bastards unsafe.
你让那些混蛋不安全了
That's why I'm nice to you.
这就是为什么我对你好的原因了
I couldn't do that without you,booth.
没有你我也做不到的, Booth
Yeah.,Um,
是的, 恩
you should be a little nicer to me,huh?
你应该对我再好点, 呃?
- I really should.  - Yeah.
- 我真的应该  - 是的
I walk in on something?
我打扰了什么了吗?
- Beignet and a caf? - cher.
- 煎饼和一杯咖啡?  - 厨师
Hospital records.
医院记录
The tox screen was negative.
毒物测试是阴性的
What?
什么?
That's impossible.
那不可能
No rohypnol,no ketamine?
没有镇定剂, 没有克他命?
Nothing but a touch of alcohol,
除了酒精什么都没有
not enough to affect a baby.
连打小孩的力气都没有
A jury is never going to believe this amnesia story.
陪审团不会相信这个健忘的故事的
Well,but it's true.
但是这是真的
Maybe this is truetoo.
也许这也是真的
Legiere tried to rape you.
Legiere想要强奸你
He was aotorious horndog.
他是只发情的公狗
We claim self-defense,cop a plea,you're out in three years.
我们声称是自卫反击 三年后你就能出来
No,I don't care what it looks like,or how you're reading the evidence,carolyn,
不, 我不在乎这像是什么 或你怎么看待证据的, Carolyn
she didn't do it.
她没有做过
Could be that's true,seeley.
那也可能是真的
You vouch for her,that's good enough for me.
你袒护她, 对我来说没关系
But,cheri,this looks bad.
但是, 事情就糟了
All you've got on your side is proof you got roughed up.
所有你的证据都表明你很冲动
These picture from the clinic,
这些是医院来的图
these x-rays.
这些X光片
New wrist.
新的腕关节
The doctor was wrong.
医生错了
He said this was a colles' fracture from a fall.
他说这是高空落下骨折造成的
This break shows surface trauma on the outside of the bone.
这个断裂表明是骨头外表面受损
This was either defensive,
这可以是自卫造成的
or someone slammed my wrist into something.
或是有人把我的腕关节撞击什么造成的
Maybe because you tried to stab him in the heart with a knife.
也许是因为你想用刀去刺他的心脏
No,think about it. If I'd alread stabbed the attacker,
不, 想想, 如果我已经刺伤了袭击者
he wouldn't have been able to break my wrist.
他不可能弄断我的手腕
I like this story.
我喜欢这故事
- What else?  - There's the mojo bag.
- 其他呢?  - 那有个符咒
I mean,someone was trying to put a forgetting spell on her.
有人想给她施健忘咒
- Booth. - Hey,I can work with that.
- Booth - 嘿, 我相信的
This is new orleans,baby. and where's my beignet?
这里是新奥尔良, 宝贝 我的煎饼在哪?
Brennan.
Brennan
John doe 361 is named rene mouton.
无名氏361号的名字是Rene Mouton
How can you be sure?
你怎么能肯定?
I looked for something that wasn't there,which turned out to be a shunt channel.
我在找一些看不到的东西, 子弹轨迹
Good work.
做的好
You understood that?
你明白?
All zack had to do was cross-check with d-mort.
Zack要做的是 再确认一次行动应答组织
I only thought of it because of hodgins.
因为Hodgins我才想到这个
I can discern particulates on the x-ray,
我能在X光片里鉴别出微粒
but I have no way of telling what they are.
但是我说不出那是什么东西
Some kind of dirt?
灰尘吗?
Okay,everybody,the word "dirt" means nothing here in the lab,scientifically.
好吧, 用科学的说法, 灰尘这个词 在这个实验室里什么都不是
Any progress on the design that was pressed into the pelvic bone?
骨盆上受到的压力模型有进展吗?
I've tried three different computer programs.
我试过了三种不同程序
I fed in the information into multiple impact scenarios,
我把信息输进了多种冲击场景里
but this isn't going to work on x-rays.
但这在X光片里行不通
I need the actual remains.
我需要实际存在的骨骸
Booth and I are looking for them as hard as we can.
Booth和我也在努力的找他们
Or,better still,you could forget the whole thing and come home.
或者, 你最好能忘掉整件事回来
Don't worry. I made bail.
别担心, 我保释了
- Bail?  - Bail?
- 保释?  - 保释?
For what?
为什么?
I told you. Don't worry.
我说过了, 别担心
The murder charge won't stick.
谋杀罪名不成立的
Whoa,whoa,whoa. Murder charge?
哇哦, 哇哦, 哇哦, 谋杀罪名?
Brennan,the next plane,okay?
Brennan, 下趟飞机, 听到了吗?
The next plane,or I'm coming down there to get you myself.
下趟飞机你回来, 不然我去接你回来
Everything's fine.
一切都好
I'm healing up satisfactorily.
我正在恢复
Bye for now.
现在再见吧
Healing up?
恢复?
you know what?
你知道吗?
This whole state of affairs where brennan just runs around fighting crime?
Brennan为了犯罪案件到处奔波?
It's stupid.
那很愚蠢
It's nuts.
那很疯狂
Don't you agree?
你不同意吗?
Go. Go.
去吧, 去吧
I'll be... fine.
我会...好的
Brennan will be fine,angela.
Brennan会好起来的, Angela
She got bail and the murder charge won't stick.
她被保释了, 谋杀罪名不成立
What is going on with her?
她是怎么回事?
Angela...
she started to change the day she met you.
她从遇见你的那天起就变了
- What?  - Well,she sees how you do it.
- 什么?  - 她看到你是怎么做事的
All fun and involvement and pizzazz.
所有的玩笑, 案件还有披萨
Big,you know?
宏大的, 你知道吗?
Big life.
宏大的人生
Booth came along and gave her the opportunity,
Booth过来给了她机会
but she got the idea from you.
但是她从你那学到的想法
Brennan wants a big life like yours.
Brennan想要你那样的宏大人生
That's how it looks to me,anyway,but what do I know?
这是我的看法, 但我知道什么?
I'm a bug guy.
我是个虫男
Bug and slime.
虫子和粘液
And dirt.
还有灰尘
Yeah. So...
是的, 那...
okay.
好吧
According to bureau files,rene mouton headed up a small voodoo church.
根据档案显示, Rene Mouton 拥有一座伏都教的教坛
By all accounts,he was a very good man.
所有的证据显示他是个好人
He rescued scores of people during katrina.
他搭救受卡特里娜飓风打击的人
Then he just disappeared.
然后就消失了
Some thought he was just swept away when the levee broke.
有人认为大堤决口时他被洪水冲走了
Why would anyone murder him?
为什么有人要谋杀他?
You know the chaos,during the evacuation.
你知道在撤退时的混乱
Could even have been for a bottle of water.
可以只是为了一杯水
Or
或是
because he was a priest.
因为他是牧师
The gris-gris box,
那个护身符包
the murder of dr. Legiere,
Legiere博士的被杀
your amnesia-- this is the work of a bokor,
你的健忘症――这是一个bokor的工作
a secte rouge sorcerer.
红色邪教巫师
Rene mouton was a houngan,
Rene Mouton曾经是一名祭司
a powerful and well-loved priest.
集权力和爱戴于一身的神父
For secte rouge to claim his soul,
为红色邪教献上了他的灵魂
this would give them influence on all the people that he influenced.
这将会给那些受他影响的教众带来影响力
Like a chain letter.
就像连锁信那样
Or in the real world, somebody who wanted his shoes.
或者在真实世界里，有人想要他的鞋子
No,booth,it makes sense.
不，Booth，这说得通
What does?
怎么说得通？
Graham and I were on the trail of a broker...
Graham和我曾经跟踪一个交易商 (英文中发音和bokor相似)...
bokor.
bokor(纠正)
And he found out,
然后被他察觉了
or secte rouge did.
或者是被红色邪教
All right,great. Then we just toss the ring into the molten river and blah,blah,right?
好吧, 好极了！然后我们就把戒指 扔进了融化的河水之类之类, 对吧
Look,in the meantime, somebody here had the ability to hide mouton's body and files.
在那同时, 这儿有人有能力 把Mouton的尸体和文件藏起来
James embry.
James Embry
- Me. - Mike doyle.
- 我 - Mike Doyle
Say you wanted to hide a particular body and you didn't want anyone to find out--
如果你想把某具尸体藏起来 而且不想让任何人找到
where would you put it?
你会把它放在哪?
If I wanted to hide a body,
如果我想藏尸体的话
I'd change the nametag on the coffin.
我会调换棺材上的名字卡
Not mouton,too young.
不是Mouton, 太年轻了
He's buried and the evidence is gone forever.
他被埋起来，证据就永远消失了
Female. Yoknow, I find that hard to believe
女性, 知道吗, 我觉得这真是难以置信
that horny little mike doyle is a voodoo sorcerer.
小Mike Doyle居然是一个巫毒教巫师
Mm-hmm.
嗯
Me,too.
我也这么想
Speaking a devel
说曹操曹操就到啊
My doll, And he's not alone.
他还有个伴
you said to avoid the police.
你说过不找警察的
Not cooperating is one thing,bones,okay? Concealing a double homicide?
不合作是一码事, Bones, 好吗？ 难道要隐瞒一个2条人命的杀人案？
We might as well give them an excuse to hang us.
我们或许也给了他们一个绞死我们的借口
Dr. Embry says that you can identify the bag of bones,
Embry博士说你可以鉴定一包骸骨
the skeletal remains belong to a man named rene mouton.
他们是一个叫Rene Mouton的骸骨
His skull is missing.
他的头盖骨找不到了
Lookto me like mike doyle was drugged; a spike was driven through his head
看起来Mike Doyle被下药了 一个大长钉插穿了他的头
during or immediately following sexual intercourse.
这发生在性交期间或者是一结束
Well,it appears that dr. Brennan,dr. Embry, and sam potter here
这么说来Brennan博士, Embry博士 和这儿的Sam Potter
are the three people who could have pulled this off.
是能够完成这事的三个人了
Sam potter brought us to the body; we called you in.
Sam Potter带我们找到了尸体 我们再通知你
Who does that leave?
谁走了?
Oh,please. There's no security in this place.
哦, 拜托，这个地方又没有警卫
Anyone could have gotten in here.
任何人都可能进到这里来
You said that mike was having sex when he died.
你说mike死时还和别人发生性关系
James,he must have been killed by the coffin girl.
James 他肯定是被这个棺材里的女孩给杀了
- What?  - What's her name?
- 什么？  - 她的名字是?
Well,I never got her name.
其实，我还不知道她的名字
Is there a mojo in doyle's mouth?
Doyle的嘴巴里有符咒吗？
- I don't feel comfortable releasing that...  - the girl is a voodoo sorcerer.
- 这让我很不舒服...  - 那女孩是巫教的巫师
She works for secte rouge.
她为红色邪教工作
Detective harding, I know this is,you know,
Harding侦探, 我知道，你也许会觉得
sounds superstitious,but...
这听起来很迷信，但是...
three ritual murders and a world-renowned anthropologist,
3个宗教杀手 和一个世界知名人类学家
who can't remember how she ended up smeared with the blood of a skinned man,
她无法记起她是如何被涂上一个
crucified to a wall with spikes.
被钉在墙上的剥了皮的男人的血
Call me superstitious.
说我迷信
Excuse me.
打扰下
May I scatter fwan ginea over mr. Mouton?
我想为Mouton先生洒上Fwan Ginea吗?
To purify his remains.
来净化他的遗体
No! No more of this voodoo crap.
不要! 别再来这些巫教的东西
I don't want you contaminating the body.
我不想让你玷污这遗体
What is it?
这是什么？
Ashes from a ritual fire pit.
仪式火坑里的骨灰
Ashes from a dove's feather,
一个鸽子羽毛的灰烬
salt mixed with holy water.
并且加了盐和圣水
Okay,okay,you know, we get the idea,just...
好吧好吧, 我们明白，只是
it should have no effect on the bones,detective harding.
它对骸骨毫无影响，Harding侦探
Fine,fine,go ahead.
随便你们, 继续好了
Whoa! Did you see that?
哇！你看到了吗？
Very interesting phenomenon.
非常有趣的现象
The electrostatic charge of the particles reacted with the bone.
这些粒子和骨头产生了静电反应
Angela was unable to recreate that pattern from the x-rays using the best technology in the world.
Angela用世界顶级的技术 也无法重建那个X光模型
Electrostatic,my ass.
静电, 见鬼
That was part of an emblem of a 1959 caddy brougham...
这是一辆1959年凯迪拉克的标志..
- oh,boy.  - What?
- 哦, 我的天  - 什么?
The voodoo shop guy owns a 1959 cadillac.
巫教商店的家伙 拥有一辆1959年的凯迪拉克
He's got a voodoo daughter.
他有个巫教女儿
You're taking my caddy? Why?
你们要带走我的凯迪拉克? 为什么?
Why? Because we have reason to believe
为什么? 因为我们有理由相信
that your caddy was used in the wrongful death of rene mouton.
你的凯迪拉克被用于谋杀Rene Mouton
You think that someone did a hit-and-run on rene mouton in my caddy?
你认为有人驾驶我的凯迪拉克 撞倒了Mouton, 然后逃跑了
Yes.
是的
Mr. Benoit,does your daughter have a boyfriend?
Benoit先生, 你女儿有男朋友了吗？
Yeah!
是的！
this him?
是他吗？
Mike doyle. Yeah. Why?
Mike Doyle, 是的，怎么？
We need to speak to your daughter...
我们需要和你的女儿谈谈
by which I mean detective harding needs to speak to your daughter.
我的意思是Harding侦探 需要和你女儿谈谈
I don't know where she is.
我不知道她在哪
Mr. Benoit,right now, she's a suspect in the murder of mike doyle.
Benoit先生, 现在开始 她就是谋杀Mike Doyle的嫌疑犯了
Why would eva kill her boyfriend?
Eva怎么可能杀她男朋友？
It's hard to explain.
这个就难解释了
She was involved in a hit-and-run.
她涉嫌一桩肇事逃逸案件
When the body surfaced at the morgue,
当尸体出现在陈尸房
she asked her boyfriend to help her hide it.
她要求她男朋友帮助她藏匿这具尸体
He refused,so she killed him.
他拒绝了，于是她杀了他
Also,she's a member of secte rouge.
而且她还是一个红色邪教教徒
No,no,no.
不, 不会的
I bet there are drugs in this shop that could knock me out,make me forget.
我打赌这商店 有能让我昏迷和失忆的药物
Eva is downstairs,praying.
Eva在楼下祈祷
Eva?
Eva,open the door.
Eva，开门
No!
不要！
Eva.
Eva
booth.
Booth
could that be mouton's skull?
这会是Mouton的颅骨？
Yes.
是的
And this could be the spike that she used on mouton and mike doyle.
而且这可能就是她在Mouton和Mike 身上用的长钉
This is the lair of bokor,
这是Bokor的墓地
someone who can call the dark spirits.
你们可以称它是黑暗的精华
This is used for ritual animal sacrifice.
这是用来做动物献祭仪式的
It was heated to red-hot first,
它先被加热到灼热
to cauterize the wound so it wouldn't bleed.
然后用来烙印这样伤口就不会流血
What,she killed herself because she knew we were coming?
什么，因为知道我们要来所以她自杀？
No,no,not my eva.
不是的，不是，这不是我的Eva
She drove the spike through her sternum?
她用长钉刺穿自己的胸？
Sternum,heart.
胸骨，心脏
Through the chest cavity,through the spine.
穿过胸腔，穿过脊骨
Can I open this?
我可以打开这个吗？
What?
那是什么？
This one holds the soul of mr. Rene mouton.
这个盒子存着Mouton先生的灵魂
I believe this one holds the soul of the bokor.
我想这个装着巫师的灵魂
Why don't you just shut up?
为什么你不就住口？
I would like to release mr. Mouton's soul, so no other bokor can use it.
我想释放Mouton先生的灵魂 这样不会有其他巫师可以用它了
No,it's evidence. Don't touch it.
不行，这是证据, 不要碰它
I raised my eva to be a houngan,a healer.
我抚育Eva成为一个女巫，一个治疗师
How could this happen right underneath my nose?
这些事怎么会在我眼皮下发生的呢？
Rebellious adolescent?
叛逆少女？
Do you remember how much of this spike
你记得我们进来的时候
was protruding through her back when we first came in?
这长钉有多长是穿过她的背部的？
Six,eight inches.
6到8寸吧
Would the fact that the spike was red-hot cause it to go through the body more easily?
加热长钉到灼热 会让它更容易穿过身体吗？
No. It might even make it harder.
不会, 这可能会让长钉更难穿过
Eva benoit did not commit suicide.
Eva Benoit没有自杀
Based on what?
理由是……？
This room isn't even 12 feet wide.
这间房子都没有12尺宽
Even if she ran at full speed and her aim was perfect,
就算她对准目标而且全速跑
no way the spike would go through her spine,
都不可能让长钉可以穿过她的身体的
unless she was pushed onto it.
除非她是被推而穿过的
He is the sorcerer.
他是个巫师
He believes he can bring her back to life.
他相信他可以让她复活
Okay,everyone, just simmer down,okay?
好的，各位，冷静下来好吗？
You're saying that he murdered his daughter thinking that he could bring her back to life?
你是在说他认为他可以让女儿复活 所以杀自己的女儿？
You find her dead,you stop looking for mouton's murderer.
你发现她死了，你不再去找 杀害Mouton的凶手了
An inch or two to the left or right,
一到两寸在左边或者右边
we would have never known it was murder.
我们也许永远不知道这是谋杀
It had to have been hard pushing her onto the spike, especially if she were resisting.
推她穿过长钉是很困难 尤其是在她抵抗的情况下
You'd have some wounds of your own.
你应该有一些自己的伤口
There's your killer.
你就是凶手
I'd really like to go home now.
我现在很想回家
Yeah,me,too-- all right, my advice,cuff mr. Wizard here,
耶, 我也是，我建议在他给你下咒之前
before he puts a spell on you.
在这里给这位巫师手铐
What,no written confession?
什么，不用书面口供吗？
You want a confession? Threaten to release his daughter's soul,
你想要一个书面口供？ 恐吓要释放他女儿的灵魂
he'll tell you everything.
他就会什么都告诉你
Dr. Temperance brennan.
Temperance Brennan教授
You leave here,you go home,
你可以离开这里回家
it does not matter. There are powers,
没关系，这里有力量
dark powers to which distance makes no difference.
不管有多远黑暗力量都不会改变的
Easy,buddy.
轻松点伙计
( Speaking foreign language )
Hey,hey,hey!
嘿嘿嘿！
( Exhaling sharply ) ( yells )
呼气
I've noticed that very few people are scary once they've been poked in the eye.
我发现很少人眼睛被戳到时还吓人
whew!
哇！
I got in the middle of a battle between two religious sects.
我被夹在两个宗教教派之间的斗争中
Benoit used hurricane katrina as a diversion to take the soul of a voodoo priest.
Benoit利用卡特里娜飓风 转移了伏都教祭司被杀的视线
And he killed his own daughter.
而且他杀了自己的女儿
Dark sorcerers suck,man.
黑巫师太糟糕了
Oh,but you know,he intended to bring her back to life.
噢，但是你知道，他打算让她复活
There's not really any such thing as spells and magic.
没有什么东西是真的咒语和魔法的
What are you talking about?
你们在说什么？
They put a forgetting hex on dr. Brennan.
他们在Brennan教授身上施遗忘咒
It wasn't the spell that made me forget;
不是什么咒语让我忘记事情的
it was the drugs-- rohypnol.
那是药物
Blood test didn't find any.
血液检验没有找到什么药物
Gamma-hydroxybutyrate?
迷奸药？
Not a trace.
没有显示
Sodium petathol?
清醒剂?
Nope.
也没有
Severe emotional trauma.
严重的精神创伤
Honey,even I think you're too strong-minded for that.
就算我也认为你对这个反应太强烈了
There were too many delays in doing my blood test--
我的血液测试迟了太久…
that,plus the adrenaline of my escape,the drugs were out of my system.
加上在我逃离时肾上腺素作用药物 就在我体内消耗完了
They put the voodoo on you,baby.
他们在你身上施咒了，宝贝
I didn't really mean to call you "baby."
我不是真的叫你"宝贝"
You guys,stop.
你们，住口
Now. I mean it.
现在，我认真的
You do believe in voodoo?
你真的相信伏都教巫术吗？
Because even if a small part of you believes in it,
因为哪怕你是部分相信它
then it has a grip.
它都可以控制住你
I do not believe.
我不相信
Maybe just a little?
也许只是一丁点？
- No.  - Good,because, you know, if you have any doubts,
- 不是   - 很好, 因为你知道如果你有任何疑问
we'll just have benoit send you back one of those little satanic mojo pouches from prison.
我们会在监狱里让Benoit 给你解释点恶魔的咒语
Booth,objects have no intrinsic power.
Booth, 事物没有内在力量的
A person's future does not depend on some thin
一个人的未来不是取决于一些事物
things are just things.
事物只是事情而已
They do not have magical meaning or powers.
他们没有神奇的意义或者力量的
Where'd you get that?
你在哪里找到的？
What does it matter?
这有什么意义吗？
It's just a thing. Right?
这只是一件物体，对吧？
My mother's earring.
我妈妈的耳环
No,uh...
不是，恩…
magical power over your future.
是影响你未来的神奇力量
Does that prove something?
这是不是可以证明点什么？
Yeah.
是的
It proves something.
它证明了些事情
--------------------------  www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents --------------------------
识骨追踪 第1季第19集 -=结束=-
bones Season 1 Episode 19
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-  翻译: chambers&macready&barry&superclark&布瓜&vicky怪 校对: sybil 时间轴: vicky8800 & starry